Name a popular
messaging app.
(No subtitles)
If you picked
WhatsApp, it's
over for you.
Make sure not
to choose the
same as me or
you're out.
Question two
press and hold
the comment
button and
select one of
the four
emojis.
(No subtitles)
If your answer
was this one,
it's over for
you. Question
three name a
type of flower.
(No subtitles)
If you picked
rose, you're
too
predictable.
Question four
pick a number
between 63 and
70.
(No subtitles)
If you picked
69, you're
done. Question
five who
appears when
you click
share, and
more.
(No subtitles)
If your answer
was your tutor,
get out. Bet
you $20 you'll
get this last
one wrong.
Question six
choose city or
countryside.
(No subtitles)
If you choose
city, you're