Name a
politician.
If you picked
Donald Trump,
keep scrolling
because you're
out. Don't pick
the same as me
or it's over.
Only 1.5%
succeed.
Question two
press and hold
the comment
button and
select one of
the four
emojis.
If you chose
this specific
emoji, you need
to get your
game up.
Question three
name a holiday.
You definitely
chose.
Christmas. Get
out. Question
four pick a
number between
five and 15.
Only a beta
like you picked
ten, you're
out. Question
five. Who
appears when
you click
share. And
more.
You better not
have chosen
your therapist.
Adios, amigo.
If you can't
get this last
question right,
you owe me a
follow.
Question six
choose sweet or
savory.
Only a beta,
like you
picked. Sweet.
Keep scrolling
because you're
out of.